ANIMAAA!
HAHAHAHAHAHAHA!
Ai!
EM To learn how to love And forget our dreams Metal bones not healing Life's a bit of pain I'm going up the rails on a crazy train I'm going up the rails on a crazy train I know that things are going wrong for me You gotta listen to my words Metal bone not healing I'm going up the rails on a crazy train You gotta listen to my words Metal bone not healing That's what we think of It's really been trouble I need to lean on To wake up And just stand up and feel it I believe it was something That just isn't fair Metal bone not healing Ruin marks to play I'm going up the rails on a crazy train I'm going up the rails on a crazy train Metal bone not healing